Mathias (Matt) Costa

Quincy, MA

tel: (617) 639-6916 email: mattiecosta@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/mattcosta7 github.com/mattcosta617

I am a Software Engineer/Web Developer with a background in production. I use my experience in production in combination with my Software Engineering experience to make programming better. My current goal is to start my journey in tech.

Skills: Javascript, HTML, CSS, Git, mongoDB, Python, REACT, Django, SQL, Postman, robo 3t, Github, Microsoft Office,

Employment History

New England Conservatory Boston, MA Assistant Stage Manager -

February 2016 - February 2019

- Changing the stage (setting orchestra, lighting, risers, working with performers)
- Locking up the Halls for the night

Freelance Lighting, Staging, Audio Technician Boston, MA *August 2010-2020*

- Worked with production companies such as: Protechs, C.I.M.S., Productions Inc., Port Lighting Systems, Symphony Hall, Tangelwood Music Festival.
- Setting up and taking down audio, video, staging, lighting, and fabrics. Lead at multiple companies setting up/take down events. Toured Spain as stage manager for the Boston Philharmonic Youth Orchestra in June 2016

Brewster Ambulance Service Jamaica Plain. MA EMT-B

December 2013-August 2014

 Providing medical care in emergency high pressure situations and in non-pressured situations. Driving Ambulance. Working with other EMT-b/Medics/Hospital staff on a daily basis to provide the best possible care to any and all patients

Volunteer Experience

Building homes and teaching English in Nicaragua, Haiti, and the Dominican Republic

Languages

Primary: English - Secondary: Spanish(intermediate)

Education

North Quincy High School: Diploma (2012)
Quincy College (some college)-Computer Science, Programming 2017
General Assembly Software Engineering 2020

Certifications

OSHA 30 Construction - Aerial Lift Certification